それでは今回はこのチョコレートオカリナを使って何曲演奏できるか
Now, with this chocolate ocarina, how many songs can I play
やってみたいと思います。
So I challenge.
1:Mary had a little lamb
2:Buzz Little Bee
溶けてる。
Has melted.
3:The Cuckoo
4:When The Saints Go Marching In
5:The Cuckoo(Once again Failure )
6:Chorus of frogs
7:Twinkle Twinkle Little Star
チョコレートだらけです。
Is full of chocolate.
8:Michael, Row the Boat Ashore
もう音がしなくなってきました。
I did not hear a sound anymore.
もうこんな風にベトベトです。
The ocarina is already sticky in this way.
何よりも
than anything else
口の中が
The inside of my mouth
大変な状態になってきました。
has become a great state
今回のチャレンジはこれで終わりにしたいと思います。
ありがとうございました。
I want to end with this challenge now. Thank you all!